Coconut [music] water coconut water
in Florida. He said I feel like a bad
I'm trying to hop on your face and it
like a motor coconut water coconut water
and make sure this cookie
does. [music]
[music]
You got a two day [singing] trial before
I take back my time and make you pay.
30-day [music] trial before I make my
mind.
[music]
It'll show you the life and find
it
cover.
>> [music]
>> Yeah. She making shake breaking that B
to the back break.
Yeah. [music]
Yeah. Crazy how you manage to make me
into a sponsor. You got me.
You got a two day trial before I take
back my time and make you [music] pay.
30day trial before I make my mind.
[music]
She want she want a [music]
crime call. No, I never
[music] make it to my lobby. It can't be
turned can't be mine.
[music]
Crazy how you manage to make me into a
sponsor. You got me.
[music] You got two back.
>> Hey y'all. Welcome. Welcome to the
vlogging vlog.
>> We are coming to you live from Puerto
Rico. Okay. And it's hot and humid, but
it's not too hot. Like this okay
weather. But y'all, we is out here for
my cousin birthday. And we going to turn
up this whole trip sun up, sun down.
Okay,
>> we in Puerto Rico turning up another
notch.
>> Another notch. It's currently 9:35,
y'all. We got here super early. We had a
long flight. We had a layover and
everything. So, whatever footage that
y'all I put in from that, I don't know
to tell you about that. But we fa to
drop our luggage off cuz we can't even
check in right now. But it's okay cuz we
got errands to run.
[music]
>> When I should have went home, only time
of the day I get to spend on my own. I
was tripping all used to sleep at your
crib. Drop right where you live and pick
you up on the [music] way. We ain't so
long. Probably put me in the past. I can
still get you wet and I can still make
you [music] laugh. You should call in to
work. If daddy too much to ask, I can
pour you up a drink. We can come
through. [music]
>> While we waiting cuz y'all we ain't got
nothing to do right now. We are going to
try this drink cuz we want to get more
if it's good. And we still up in
Walmart. So we need to try it now then.
Thanks to Mari thinking that you know
>> this rum
>> me helping for her.
>> Okay.
>> Cute. Yeah.
>> Got a little straws right here.
>> Mhm. It's giving Capri some for adults.
They got other flavors, but I see people
buying the passion fruit one a lot this
whole trip. Liquor, lick, lick, lick.
Drink, drink, drink.
>> We started early. We drinking that
party.
>> Let's see.
>> Life works. No reaction. No, you need to
try it first.
>> It's juice. Oh, hell no.
>> Exactly.
>> We going to tap back in later cuz we not
doing nothing and my camera going to be
dying soon. So y'all probably going to
catch us when we checking in finally.
[music and singing]
I think you want [music] you should make
me your girl.
If it's something that you need, [music]
then baby come and share my world. Share
my world. If it's something that [music]
you want, come and take a walk with me.
[singing]
Everything that you need, [music] I got
it right here, baby.
Now it's obvious you need a friend. I'm
[music] going to hold you down. Be that
one to share everything. No one's
around. Baby, [music] come tell me your
secret. Tell me all your dreams. Cuz I
can see you need to trust. [music] You
can trust in me.
Daddy,
>> so [music] just call me whenever you're
lonely. [singing]
Daddy, I'll be your friend. Then I can
be your [music]
make your girl. [singing]
[music]
>> Wait, Victor, you really did this?
>> Yes, I did that. We did that. Oh, here's
Maggie
and Mari. But what's our names for
tonight?
>> My name Maria.
>> Mhm.
>> I can't.
>> Oh my god.
>> What's your name for tonight?
>> Els Moralda.
>> And we got
>> And I'm Selena.
Hey y'all. So, I just dipped from them.
Um, so I can actually talk to y'all cuz
I haven't talked to y'all in a long time
and you probably want to beat me up like
but you can't. So, hey, I missed you.
What you been doing? How's life been
treating you? Like, we not into it or
nothing, right? Like, I could still
like, you know, I can still pop on your
screen or you mad.
No shade. But I'm going to do my makeup,
y'all, cuz we supposed to be going out.
It is currently
9:02. Okay. And then in my cup, I have
this um Puerto Rican rum cocktail drink.
This day version of cup water. I promise
you.
>> All of a sudden, I hear this agitating,
grading voice.
>> Oh [\h__\h] your boy.
[music]
>> Hey y'all, we f to go out. ass.
>> Yes. And I'm going to do my makeup.
>> Dry around.
>> It's 9:00. I rather already have it
done. Take my time.
>> Your makeup?
>> Yeah. I'm going to start.
>> No, you fine. I'm in your room. But no,
I told him you fine. The one who almost
crashed.
>> No, really.
>> I told him he fine. No, you're not.
Actually,
>> y'all earlier this man almost crashed
into the [\h__\h] car ahead of us.
>> Yes.
>> He got his bike. They drive crazy. No,
>> he drive crazy.
>> He drive crazy.
>> Okay. When you going to come for this
perm? You want to you going to bring it
back or you want to get it out?
>> You should really come to the bathroom
with me.
>> That sound a little [laughter] like you
want me to come to the bathroom with
you.
>> So we could
>> Why is you saying that on camera?
>> Huh?
>> Why you saying that on camera?
>> Yeah, it's not.
>> But no, but it's not no room for real.
>> It's not fine. You don't want to go to
the bathroom with me. [\h__\h] you. [\h__\h]
you.
>> I'mma come. Wait, what if I ask?
>> So, do you want me to come or not?
>> Come.
>> But I got to take all this stuff up and
now me
>> and then but I got to put my m my camera
on the TV. I mean the mirror.
>> All right.
>> All right. Can you grab this for me? The
primer is in the primer is right here.
>> Hey, perfect. What do you need me to
grab
>> this? I was going to say like I just
asked her can she grab something for me?
But yeah, we finn to switch. So hold on.
>> Okay y'all, we back.
[music]
hands around my waist. [music] Just let
the music.
>> Give me the mic.
>> Yes, I do. Ask your profession. You say
something like I'm dragging.
>> No, I'm going say it to you. [\h__\h] the
confession.
>> You say something out like your
profession. I'm dragging you out.
>> Come on. Just give me now cuz I'm going
TO SAY [\h__\h] OH, LET'S GO.
>> OH, THE GIRLS ARE FIGHTING WAY.
[screaming]
the
baby.
I don't SEE
I don't see the NURSING [screaming]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] the
>> Yeah.
>> Hey y'all.
>> I
just drag that [\h__\h] Hold on.
>> Hello,
babe.
>> Okay. Anyways, yeah. Let's drag that
[\h__\h] on
the entrance right now.
>> Hello.
>> Oh, I'm on mute.
>> G, I'm tweaking so bad right now. Good.
Okay. Bye, guys. I have to go.
>> I wear other one, but like,
>> bro, my camera been up in here. I just
went and fought. I just beat her ass. I
don't give a [\h__\h] cuz girl, don't
don't ever. She talking about
confessional. Okay, the confession. I
hope my makeup is coming out good cuz
Mari told me to come in here and then
she not even in here. So, I was like,
[\h__\h] But I think I want to finish this
off camera. I'mma just come back when
I'm done my makeup. I'mma show y'all.
This is how it look before. Okay.
I'm I'm I'mma mess with you. You let me
know. Did I eat or No. If it look a
little messed up, ignore it. Okay.
Hey y'all. My makeup is done. I think I
don't know. I might have to go back in.
But I'm going to tell y'all about my
outfit. It's in this bag. This bag I got
from Sheen. Okay. So, I'm wearing these
heels
also from Sheen. Purse from Sheen.
This is a bracelet. And then this is a
belt that I'm going to wear around my
waist. And I'mma put on a black tube top
dress. So, I'm going to get ready cuz
everybody had their clothes on but me. I
just finished. I hope my makeup look
good. If it don't, blame it on alcohol.
But I'll be back. Hold on. Do you know
what? [music] I just came here, but now
we're rocking
[music and singing]
around.
>> We going to take our little shot.
Now we're face to face.
[music]
>> [music]
>> It's so HARD TO PICK ONE, [screaming]
BUT IF I GOT TO I WANT TO [screaming]
YOU here with
>> Where YOUR FRIEND AT? WHY YOUR FRIEND
NOT WITH YOU?
>> YEAH, you got to slow down CUZ I DON'T
PLAY THAT. We not
>> where we going to wait for her.
>> Okay.
>> All right.
>> I know. I
>> No, it's not true. She walking through.
>> Y'all got to be at the same pace. Be
safe.
>> Thank you.
>> No, for real. I'm surviving. I NEED
>> BUT FOR REAL, I TOOK that whole shot
like a real What is talking about?
>> It's right OVER THE THE PLACE WE WENT TO
IS RIGHT OVER HERE.
SHE DON'T WANT TO EAT. SHE WANT TO
PARTY.
>> Night sister,
>> right? 1942.
[screaming]
>> HI, POLICE.
>> HI.
>> You see the police giving ME A TICKET? I
DON'T GIVE A [\h__\h]
>> WE WE ain't We didn't mean to do that.
>> These people don't give no [\h__\h]
>> FOR REAL.
>> WHO THEY COMING FOR? Who that in the
bag? Who that in the bag?
>> That
in the bag. Who that in the [screaming]
bag?
Who that in the bag? WHAT THE
[laughter]
>> She talking about where
I'M
a seen.
>> Who that with the waves, [screaming]
y'all? It's probably so loud in my No,
I'm probably loud and my camera. I've
been vlogging for too long, but y'all
need this. Who that? What? LET ME PUT
THAT OVER. Go ahead. My backing better.
She came through WITH A PUERTO RICAN
VLOG. THEY GOING TO RUN us over on a
motorcycle.
The motorcycle going to run us over and
[\h__\h] I'm like, back. She back on the
two. Put that in the bag. PUT THAT IN
THE BAG. Put that in the bag.
[screaming]
>> Hi, Emily.
>> Hola, Emily.
>> Emily, the longest snake. But this Emily
at 7 months.
>> That's her mom.
>> Look at Ooh, this her mom. Oo.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> Oh, she big. Where? Where the mom at?
>> My home IS RESTING.
>> EMILY OUTSIDE TONIGHT. I KNOW. THAT'S
RIGHT.
We just be going on fire quest, y'all.
You know ended up at the Oo, that that
music bumping. Let's see what time it
is.
[music]
>> We just came out the club, bro. It's
like
time
for dinner.
>> No, we eating.
>> I don't know.
>> Is there any food along the way? Okay.
Put it in Google Translate.
>> McDonald.
>> McDonald's.
>> See, let's go there.
He said burger.
>> No, McDonald's.
>> McDonald's.
>> A donut.
>> Yes.
>> Oh my god.
>> No. We going to eat for dinner. Okay.
Going to make sure make sure we fed
anyway. [snorts]
>> Yes.
>> 3:42. My phone going to die. But it's
okay. We going to go inside.
>> We done did Next Club. Another club. No
sleep.
>> Next club. Another club. Another club.
>> McDonald's.
>> Got to get up at 10:00 a.m.
>> No. No. Not 10 a.m.
>> Not 10:00 a.m. Exactly.
>> And what time is it?
>> But if everybody just go home and get in
the shower right now, then we can
probably get up at like 8:45.
>> Who going to be the responsible one that
wake everybody up? That's my thing.
>> You got to set the alarm.
>> Oh yeah. Okay. So my phone pajamas I
mean not pajamas. We only put on bathing
suit.
>> Yeah. My um And then how far the place
is?
>> Let me check.
>> I got to look social.
and see what I'm going to
>> wear in
>> cuz this outfit was really for
>> the menu. The menu.
>> Oh, I know what I want. A hot and spicy
chicken.
>> See, I be seeing people get that. But
you get the regular one.
>> I thought you was posting like a like
the celebrities.
>> What happened?
>> I just kept saving the videos.
>> Exactly. Now post them.
>> Post them.
>> But these [\h__\h] kept getting in and I
kept
>> them [\h__\h] He them [\h__\h]
>> for real
>> them not our [\h__\h] So
>> you the birthday
>> not our problem.
>> So like I don't I don't see the
correlation.
>> Exactly. [laughter]
>> No for real.
>> Yes. Get our McDonald's poppy
chicken.
>> What you getting girl? If nothing if
they don't hurry the [laughter]
>> bro's
quart.
>> I want a hot and spicy meat chicken.
[laughter]
>> He said give me that $5 meal deal.
>> For real. Y'all don't have that out here
like
get here now.
>> Ace now.
This second.
>> What is taking up so
trap house booming? Mhm.
>> I'm going to take me a shower. Okay. I
just ate mommy and we got to get up at
like 8. I'm going to talk to y'all. We
had a full day.
[music]
>> [\h__\h]
you can see why [music]
don't
I'm shaking ass then I laugh. Let me
stop trying. [music] We in the pool top
list girls
hit us. [music] We don't need cash. I'm
with the girls going wild.
[music]
White girl wasted in the pool but naked
with my twin. We in Vegas [music] top.
[music]
>> Y'all we going to go to dinner. Well,
not dinner. It's was basically dead
because it's late.
>> They ain't take these two shots now. Me
and Mari, y'all seen us down there.
These is full. Why these ain't get
>> I couldn't understand what you saying.
Back in the day all these little walking
to me. I don't play sports. If I did
about how [\h__\h] or can't get no pass.
Cut a [\h__\h] off cuz he thought he was
going to have to show that I leave his
ass. You know that. Now we going to
finally go eat. Finally. [\h__\h] is
sitting around here to throw up cuz my
stomach empty. It's 5:38. First meal of
the day.
>> We had a cupcake but doesn't ain't no
meal. So
>> cupcake and huh?
>> Cupcake and liquor.
>> Me and Mari been starving.
>> Cake and liquor. Mari look good y'all.
See
whole crew been looking good the whole
time. But the trip just started. Hola.
>> Give me the pen.
>> Yeah.
>> Sing it.
>> [music]
>> Yeah. Why? [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Take it away, Poy.
>> Go.
>> I'mma check back in when we make it to
the restaurant.
spicy.
>> You don't know nothing. [laughter]
We blocking the second we get out this
assig. [music]
[music]
Let me know if y'all feeling it. I'm
getting
>> like Do any of these look good to you?
>> Cuz I don't know. I don't go on TikTok
and look at what's on there.
>> Yeah, we just ordered our
>> We stayed there for like got the sister
got salad and I got a chicken plate and
some rice.
>> I'm not going to eat I'm not going to
eat nothing. The menu didn't have
nothing.
Like they like actually make
>> Now y'all can see my food cuz y'all
could not see at first but do it look
good.
>> The camera eat first.
>> That is not her name. These might be
good.
They probably
>> are they
okay? I'm back y'all. My food was not
good.
I'm ready to go drink liquor cuz I was
okay when I was drinking the liquor.
When I want to eat the food, the food
don't want to be good. That's why I'mma
drink the liquor.
>> Bro, the hell.
>> You know the liquor going to be nasty.
The food I'm expecting to be good and
it's nasty. No.
Hey y'all, don't mind my makeup.
Actually, mind it. Judge me. [laughter]
Judge me. But I don't care. So today I'm
just minding my business.
>> Why the [\h__\h] you wasn't?
>> I was I got mentioned in this. She
mentioned me and then you going to tag
me on Tik Tok and Instagram. Like
girl and out of all the videos you could
have used. You could have used straight
videos of me.
>> This girl been messy all day being
messy.
>> You're a liar.
>> That girl's a liar.
>> Being messy all day. So like Karma got
her ass back.
>> What? And
>> how was I being messy? [laughter]
How was I being messy?
>> Prank calling people.
>> Girl,
>> um,
>> they asked me to do it.
>> Talking about Kha.
>> Who? Kesha. My whole You wasn't going to
say nothing.
>> Whoa.
>> Who is Kesha?
>> Um,
>> who is Kha? That
>> you know who the Kha is?
>> No, I don't.
>> More than a Kisha.
>> Oh, yeah. That's a [laughter]
That's her name.
>> Bro, that's how you know I'm not messy
because I don't even
>> I'm not messy cuz I didn't know how to
do no collar ID,
>> you know. Now 67. How you going to
forget?
>> Look at her.
>> 67. [laughter] I want Chanel,
>> bro.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> But she just lied and tried to say I was
messy.
>> I'm not done with my professional.
>> Oh my god. She
she being messy and that's why
they posted
[laughter]
a trailer. But um what's his name,
>> bro? But she talking about she made me
an intro. Why the [\h__\h] would that be my
intro? [laughter]
Don't f I'm thinking somebody I'm like
somebody made me an intro already. Then
I see some [\h__\h] Yeah,
>> I see some [\h__\h] bro. What do that
got to do with anything?
>> Messy
>> for real. That's his page.
>> That's his fake page.
>> Cuz I was I was cool with you.
>> She can go, y'all.
>> You trying to have you come to the
birthday?
>> Savia got me editing her pictures.
>> I asked and I gave her a cupcake.
Actually, she called me a fat [laughter]
[gasps]
>> cuz she tried to call me a liar.
>> She called me a fat
>> tried to call me
>> after she gave me the cupcake combo. She
going to tell me, "Can you give me
>> Let me speak my pe. Shut up.
>> You trying to speak?"
>> She called me a fat and she said, "Get
to work." And threw the iPad at me.
>> Tell the whole I don't like people that
lie like that.
>> Am I right? Semi wrong.
>> That's I'm going to show you the the
before and after. So, this is after. Oh,
shoot. Wait. I'm going to have to tap
this rings like my band's on.
>> Damn. My phone on one. Let me
>> after
>> and before.
>> Before and before.
>> Y'all think she going to love it? I
think she going to love it because I did
it. And
>> wait, let me read the comments
>> on what?
>> Let me see what they said. Somebody said
before and before [laughter]
[gasps]
[laughter]
>> she did her hardest.
>> Okay, let me show you. Come look.
>> Let me stop. My makeup is already done.
[laughter]
>> Bro, come look. Where are you going?
>> Is on one. Hold on.
>> I am.
>> Are you ready?
>> Yeah.
>> What you laughing for? You trolling me.
>> No. Like I feel like I did so good on
this.
>> No, you done it.
>> That's not why you laughing.
>> Like y'all look. Look how clean the
background looks.
>> You're a liar. Let me see.
>> Get out. [laughter]
>> Why would you do that?
>> This is insane.
>> Talk about that. Get to work. Oh, you
were so wrong.
>> You were so wrong. I SAID IT.
>> YOU SAID IT. YOU SAID IT to me.
>> I said that.
>> See, that's her karma. There's her
[laughter] karma.
>> Wait, what the was that?
>> Your your inventory.
>> I don't give a
>> All her inventory just fell out.
>> I don't give a But yeah, y'all. She's
aing bully. And
>> I did not I said them words. Yes.
Correct. But I didn't say it like that.
>> She literally How else can you say get
to work? I didn't say that.
>> I'm just a victim.
>> I'm just going through it. She's just a
bully.
>> You a manipulator. She gaslighting on.
If you believe that, you goofy.
>> Then she left the room talking about I'm
not giving you aing cupcake. You get up
and get it yourself. So I'm like, okay.
>> And I went and got the cupcake and gave
it to her
>> and added fat. Get to work.
>> I did not say that.
>> After she just had me eating empanadas
and tequila for three days straight.
>> Well, you're not going to eat nothing in
a minute.
Yeah, y'all heard that.
>> Then she over there so snatched. I don't
feed her. That's why. [laughter]
>> Yeah, I be getting starved
>> and it's working.
>> I had to sneak off and get um $65 off
and you ate.
>> I did.
>> Okay, that's your
>> But yeah, y'all. You probably going to
come back. Um when we going to come
back?
>> At the club. Probably. at the club.
[laughter]
>> We in Puerto Rico. Turn it up another
notch.
>> I want to see you bust down. Click it
up.
>> Busting it up.
>> That pop that clut.
[screaming]
[laughter]
>> The club here.
>> No, for real. We we had the club at
home.
>> Y'all see how she trying to get out of
editing [laughter]
>> now? The way you've been holding the
thing. I think you scared to even let me
touch it
>> after you did this. [laughter]
>> Maybe. [clears throat] Let me learn.
>> Bro, when it was for New Year's, y'all
know she took them pictures and she
edited them quick.
She probably was excited to do it. I'm
going to n See, I'm You going to make me
cry.
Why would you say that to me?
>> Give me a hug. Just give me a
>> No, you steal my yak.
>> But low key, they do need to pay a
couple Spanish songs. Like, why I'm in
Puerto Rico
>> and you not playing you not
you not playing
>> and then who what was that? What club
was that? Why Kemp gonna try to lie and
say Drake coming up for his album
release party?
>> No, for real. Y'all going to the
>> You can't afford Drake on his album
release day. [laughter]
You don't know Aubrey.
You know
>> cuz I wouldn't have knew if he was in
Houston.
>> Yeah, I already been drinking and you
need to come.
>> FIRST OF ALL, HOLD ON. HOLD ON. I'M
GOING TO DO A FREE HOLD ON. HAVE YOU
ever you haven't talked to the vlog at
all?
>> I think I have
>> my YouTube.
>> I don't know.
>> You had her camera.
>> Hey y'all.
>> We on her birthday trip. She haven't
talked to y'all.
>> My birthday at 12:00. We've been having
a blast. I'm not going to lie to y'all.
It's been the best.
>> We don't want the trip to end.
>> We don't want this trip.
>> It's only day two.
>> Like, I'm so sad that tomorrow's our
last day. We got to do it soing big
tonight, bro. We like, bro, I'm telling
you, this is this trip has been one for
the books. We have not wasted one hour
of our time
>> for real. And everybody pictures coming
out good too.
>> We've been snapping on the pictures like
when I'm telling you now we got to go
take another trip cuz this content that
we've been giving y'all so t bro
>> that we just got to keep it coming like
>> and they going to want it too
>> like like my feed just looks bright and
colorful. I'm gonna I'm gonna save that.
What's the Oh,
she going to rap and [laughter]
bro. You That's why we need the mic.
That's so irritating. Yeah.
Yes. We in Puerto Rico, Canada another
notch.
She just got got.
>> What?
>> She just got got. What? We kic that
[\h__\h] out the spot.
That [\h__\h] is a bop.
But guess what? We are not.
>> We are not.
>> Yep. That's why you're her cool fly.
>> But guess what? We not. We the egg girl
and we run the world. We in Puerto Rico
and we do a twirl. We got the [\h__\h]
They on our body. They standing waiting
for US IN A LOBBY. [screaming]
>> [laughter]
>> YOU.
>> LET ME FIND OUT.
>> SHE GOING TO GET US OUT THE HOOD.
[laughter]
>> Hold on. I'm going to I'm going to I'm
going to go take ME SOMETHING CUZ I'M
GOING HEY, LET ME GO GET ONE OF THEM.
>> BRO, LET ME GET ANOTHER ONE.
>> FOR REAL. I GOT TO FILL MY cup back up.
>> Bro, you going to just SHOW THEM
EVERYTHING. [screaming]
>> WE OUT.
WE ONLY GOT TWO LEFT.
>> OH MY GOSH. EVERYBODY TAKE A SIP.
>> This feel like,
[laughter]
>> bro. No. That's crazy. Okay. I I got
this much though.
>> I got two more here. I'll hit it. I HIT.
>> OH YEAH. HEY,
she [laughter]
>> It's meant for us to drink, y'all. It's
four.
Okay, cool. I'm probably going to have
to touch up my makeup again. Is you
twerking in the background?
>> Yeah, this dress is just
>> right. What you going to put on?
>> People order piñata.
>> Pia. Oh, hell no. Pia like the
>> No, she mean pott
pinata.
>> Yeah.
>> What? Pinata.
>> I haven't seen
>> the thing you hit. Oh, a pinñata.
>> Yeah.
>> Don't piss me off.
>> Do not piss me off.
>> I don't want you pissy up in here now.
[laughter]
>> I'm thinking he's talking about a
[\h__\h] the pasta.
>> No, that's what I was trying to say. She
not talking about that, but I forgot.
>> Yeah, my mind stopped working.
>> Pa is crazy.
>> Slime get them
for y'all. Hey y'all going a whole lot
better.
>> We waiting for our table. [music] So we
just got some empanadas from some little
shop.
>> My soul of adding [music]
aart
[music]
>> y'all. Mari dropped the bottle
[laughter]
that we just gotottle. But it's okay
because this pin colada is so good. Our
table ready. So we trying to chug it cuz
we already know like they is not going
to let us have it. So we going to come
back when we at the restaurant.
>> We got some French toast eggs and
sausage.
>> What you got? Cinnamon roll. Cinnamon
toast. I mean cinnamon roll. Yeah.
Cinnamon roll. Yeah. French toast.
>> Yeah. We got the same thing.
>> This got empanadas. [laughter]
>> Mind you, we just ate some empanadas and
she got some more empanadas and fruit
and a pina coladas.
>> Yeah, you know,
[screaming]
[singing]
[music]
two. I like to drink with Mari cuz Mari
[music] is my mate. I like to drink with
Mari cuz she gets it down at eight.
Seven [singing] 6 5 4 3 2 1
>> I like
to
get down
6 5 4 3 2 1
Yeah, she going to need that.
>> Okay, Maggie.
>> I sit with my water.
>> Yeah, [clears throat] that exactly drop
that water
ain't got no water.
[laughter]
>> You need it. You need it more than me.
You need it more than me. Girls are
[laughter]
>> Come on for my camera. Like don't take
forever.
>> 1 2 3. I like to drink with Maggie cuz
Maggie is my mate. I like to drink with
Maggie cuz she gets it down at 8 7 6 5
4.
[laughter]
>> Come on. Let's go. Yeah, you don't have
[\h__\h]
>> I LIKE
[laughter]
I LIKE TO DO CUZ SHE GET EIGHT seven
five.
Bro, what the
>> Get her slushie, please. Like, we need a
nanny for you now.
I didn't know that we had children on
the trip. I thought this was a adult
only trip. I did NOT KNOW. OH, OKAY.
>> NOW, HERE I AM,
>> Y'ALL. I am so hot off that drink. Like,
this is insane,
>> y'all. We got the drink again.
>> Yeah, we rebought the one that she
broke. But I'm hot. Like, I feel my
liquor. I need to sit down.
>> How you feel?
>> I feel amazing. Like I do this [\h__\h] for
real. I forget.
>> She al I love me some
and I haven't really been drunk this
like I'm trying to get up from the last
day. So
>> yep. How you feel?
>> Yeah.
>> I feel like a bad ass [\h__\h] You know
I'm not my girl has not been drinking
>> and has she hasn't touched her.
>> I've been strung off drugs. [laughter]
[gasps]
>> I've been doing getting into other
stuff,
>> bro.
>> And yeah. So, she's she's good for the
most part. For the most part. Okay. How
about you? How you feel?
>> I'm feeling very loose.
[laughter]
>> That sounds about right.
>> You know what that mean?
>> She's happy to be here.
>> We going to go back to the Oh, no. We
going to go grab a couple things. Then
we going to come back to the B&B.
>> Wait, what are we grabbing?
>> So we can smoke.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> We going to
>> girl. And you're still doing this good,
too. So
>> the whole thing
>> exactly.
>> I need you to take at least five hits.
>> You want us to drink? We want you to
smoke.
>> I don't get another,
>> bro.
We smoke the kind of turn.
>> My chains on.
>> What's your name?
>> Um,
last
[laughter]
Okay.
No. Say
>> can I explain
>> bro?
>> Look at it.
Look at this. No.
>> No. But he's a boy.
>> I CAN'T EVEN say it.
>> What the he says this?
[screaming]
>> LOOK.
[laughter]
>> [screaming]
>> Take that shot.
>> Yep. Take that. What? You ain't say it.
[screaming]
[laughter]
>> Y'all stop it.
>> Apple.
>> Yeah, that's apple. I know that.
>> Apple of You're the apple of his eye.
>> I know how to say pendo. [laughter]
This home
[laughter]
[music]
me
I [music] want you to scream not in a
bad way but you let take you to a new
place. Close your eyes and go [music] to
sleep. I don't
know, baby. [music] I want you to drink.
>> Excuse me.
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
>> No, it just tastes too like
>> Okay. It's fishy.
>> Yeah. Got it.
>> Can I switch it out for a chicken? Thank
you.
>> See? [laughter]
I don't know what's wor
>> or a llama
>> or [laughter]
you laughing loudly.
>> Y'all having a competition.
>> Oh my god.
>> They having a competition right now.
>> Stupid [laughter] in this place. Like
>> stop it.
>> See,
>> bro. Get out.
>> Y'all have no laughing. Mama, [laughter]
>> you good job on life. Zulu is up there.
You [\h__\h] are dumb. And I didn't even
process Mari said that till today. She
was like, is this [\h__\h] really looking
at this man and say like [laughter]
what?
>> I got it right over here, man. Happy
birthday over here.
>> Thank you.
>> Let's sing happy birthday.
>> Things I want to say.
>> Okay. 1 2 3. I want to say happy
birthday to you.
>> I want to say happy
>> Thank you.
>> Now, close your eyes and make a wish
and blow out your candles.
>> I just want to thank all of y'all for
coming out on my trip. Like, this has
been so fun. I've had a wall. Like
>> I'm honestly about to cry right now
thinking about the amazing time that
we've shared together with each other.
So like stay blessed and I love y'all
[laughter]
>> and we love you more.
>> I know.
>> Mind you, Maggie [snorts] loves her the
most. Like really [laughter]
>> we so for real. Maggie can't eat, can't
sleep, can't breathe without Na. But
whatever. I eat, sleep, drink.
>> No, you don't. You do it with her.
>> No, I don't.
>> Yes, you do.
>> I'm going to post some pictures.
>> I bet you I bet you was eating, but that
stomach still
>> Yeah, I told y'all it go straight to
her. It don't go nowhere else.
>> I'm on my way. Oh, this a girl. Her name
is Demar.
>> Marus.
>> She not here.
>> You can sit right here. Go to Marcus.
>> Go to Marcus. Go Marcus.
Either food or feed [laughter]
the dog. [laughter]
>> We got to keep it safe for you.
It's going to be gone.
>> I didn't see nothing,
>> bro. Okay, I'm going to click post. I'm
scared. Glattus, post it now.
>> Is this our [\h__\h] right here,
>> bro? Now you got
>> stop playing with me. [laughter]
>> Go to get out of your ass.
>> My music,
[laughter]
>> G. I tried to have record this whole
trip.
>> I've been right here recording this
whole time.
>> It's not working.
>> A you have a USB cord.
>> Okay. Acappella,
[music] baby.
We go zero to 100 [\h__\h] real quick.
[music] Maybe on that rap and pay the
bill [\h__\h] I don't feel that [\h__\h] Not
even a little bit. Oh lord. Know
yourself, know your worth, [\h__\h] My
action being louder than my words,
[\h__\h] I still [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] Oh lord.
>> That's all for this video. I hope you
enjoyed it. Okay.
>> Cuz we sure did.
>> Yeah. And we gonna see you sometime, you
know, sometime. Like,
>> yeah,
>> I don't know when.
>> You know, we got up our sleeve. We pop
out.
>> But thank you for watching. Like,
comment, and subscribe for more. Bye.